Guide to the Stanford News Service Audiovisual Recordings SC1125
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Videorecordings, 1936-2011; Series 2
  - GMA Site Survey, 09/01/1993; 93-0901-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    [No further information is available. It might be a tape scouting for locations of the Good Morning America shoot in November. ]
  - Stanford / Washington University Game, Lexus, 09/04/1993; 93-0904-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    News Story from KGO-TV (ABC) San Francisco, 1:41 PM, 3:00
  - Alvin Rabushka Interview, Israel Spending Policies, 09/19/1993; 93-0919-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 00:14:30
    Alvin Rabushka with Hoover Institution at Stanford University is interviewed on Inside Business, CNN at 11:30pm. This was recorded by Advertising Information Services.
  - Michael McFaul, Alian Enthoven, News clips, 09/21/1993 - 09/23/1993; 93-0921-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    1. Segment with Michael McFaul, McNeil-Lehrer News Hour, 9/21/93, WNET, 7:00 PM, (20:20), Yeltsin Parliamentary Crisis 2. Segment with Alian Enthoven, McNeil-Lehrer News our 9/23/93, WNET, 7:00 PM, (45:10), President Clinton's Health Plan
  - Good Morning America at Stanford, 11/10/1993; 93-1110-2; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Good Morning America, an ABC television show, filmed at the Stanford campus. [No more information is available about this show.]
  - ABC's "Good Morning America" visits Stanford, 11/10/1993; 93-1110-4; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Stanford Football 1993, 12/00/1993; 93-1200-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 00:11:00
    Football recruiting tape. It contains a card of Scott Schuhmann, Athletic Services Coordinator
  - Stanford Promo Fall 1994, 94-0000-2; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Stanford Promo, Fall 1994 [No further information is available. It was labeled as ZZ0116, with Condoleezza Rice, and as U-Matic tape. It is vhs.]
  - Opening of Stanford Linear Accelerator, 01/11/1994; 94-0111-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    News Stories about the Opening of the Asymmetric B-Factory at the Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, VHS Dub
  - Healthcare Education Network, Tribute to Peter Bing, 01/11/1994; 94-0111-2; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 00:14:27
    Healthcare Education Network, Tribute to Peter Bing Dub, Audio: 1&2 Mono Job# 1103 TCN:2123 Peter Bing, class of 1955, was a chairman of Stanford's board. He funded the Bing Nursery School at Stanford and other building projects. A post-it note on the case states: Background for Uncommon Man - Mr. C will introduce this tribute to Peter Bing. There is also a card for Sandra Detert Cover at Stanford Associates with a note to return the tape to her. Produced by: San Francisco Production Group, 550 Bryant Street, San Francisco, Ca 94107 415-495-5595
  - SLAC, B-Factory Inauguration, 01/11/1994; 94-0111-3; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 01:10:00
    Inauguration of the Asymmetric B-Factory at Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (SLAC).
  - Farm Subsidies and Loans, Nightline, 02/14/1994; 94-0214-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    News story from Nightline, ABC-TV Network, 11:30 PM 30:00
  - Storage of Hazardous Waste on Stanford Campus, 02/15/1994; 94-0215-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 00:02:18
    "Storage of Hazardous Waste on Stanford Campus" News Story, Good Morning San Jose, KNTV-TV (ABC), San Jose, 6am, 2:18
  - Minority Administrators, 04/13/1994; 94-0413-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Story from: Eyewitness News, KPIX-TV (CBS) San Francisco, 10:00 PM 4:14
  - Chicano Students Protest at Stanford, 05/04/1994 - 05/05/1994; 94-0504-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    News clips from: Newscenter Four, KRON-TV (NBC) San Francisco, 6:00 PM, 2:03 News Eleven at Five, KNTV-TV (ABC) San Jose 5:00 PM 2:02 World News CNN-TV, Cable, 10:00 PM 2:26
  - The 103rd Annual Commencement at Stanford University, 06/11/1994 - 06/12/1994; 94-0611-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    This includes Baccalaureate Service and Senior Class Day Luncheon Highlights. Stephen Carter was the speaker.
  - Japan's Royal Couple Visit Stanford, 06/22/1994 - 06/23/1994; 94-0622-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    VMS (Video Monitor Services of America) tape contains stories about the Japanese Royalty visit to Stanford. Insert of clips: 1.) Channel 7 News, 6/23/94, KGO-TV (ABC) San Francisco, 11:30 AM, 1:35; 2.) Midday, 6/23/94, KRON-TV (NBC) San Francisco, 11:30 AM, 4:25; 3.) Midday San Jose, 6/23/94, KNTV-TV (ABC) San Jose, 11:30 AM, 2:20; 4.) Channel 3 Reports, 6/23/94, KCRA-TV, (NBC), Sacramento, 12:00 PM, 2:30; 5.) Eyewitness News, 6/23/94, KPIX-TV (CBS), San Francisco, 12:00 PM, 4:10; 6.) Channel 7 News, 6/23/94, KGO-TV (ABC) San Francisco, 5:00 PM, 1:08; 7.) Live at Five, 6/23/94, KRON-TV (NBC), San Francisco, 5:00 PM, 1:00; 8.) News 11 at Five, 6/23/94, KNTV-TV (ABC), San Jose, 5:00 PM, 1:00; 9.) Eyewitness News, 6/23/94, KPIX-TV (CBS) San Francisco, 5:00 PM, 2:25; 10.) Eyewitness News, 6/23/94, KPIX-TV (CBS) San Francisco, 6:00 PM, 2:09; 11.) Ten O'Clock News, 6/23/94, KTVU-TV (IND) Oakland, 10:00 PM 2:11; 12.) Eyewitness News, 6/23/94, KPIX-TV (CBS) San Francisco, 10:00 PM, 2:27; 13.) NewsCenter 46, 6/23/94, KCCN-TV (CBS) Monterey, 11:00 PM, 0:30; 14.) News 11 Nightside 6/23/94, KNTV-TV (ABC) San Jose, 11:00 PM 0:27; 15.) Morning Drive 6/22/94, KCBS-AM San Francisco, 6:00 3:35
  - Mass customization: conversations with innovators in manufacturing, 2000; 00-0000-3; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 00:20:25
    Music, Jonathan Norton; executive producer/faculty advisor, Diane E. Bailey. Allison Dufty, narrator. Presents a series of case studies in mass customization and demonstrates why it requires companies to rethink old assumptions regarding efficiency and competitiveness. Audio: Ch 1 & 2 Mono Mix
  - InterChange: Camarillo, Albert, 01/28/2000; 000128-IC; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 00:27:45
    Interchange: Albert Camarillo Alan Acosta, director of university communications at Stanford, hosts this half-hour conversation with Albert Camarillo, professor of history and director of the Center for Comparative Study in Race and Ethnicity. TSC Archive Number: 2000-763
  - Stanford Admission video, 09/07/2000; 00-0907-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 17:47
    Office of Undergraduate admission
  - Stanford Presents Convocation 2000, #00-131, 09/27/2000; 00-0927-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 00:58:55
    Convocation with speech by President John Hennessy. Labeled as Compliments of Randy Bean at The Stanford Channel. It also has a note: 10/13 3:10 PM Jack, Matt Owen w/ Govt & Comm Relations called. Please call him @ next week. 5-3:30. Thanks, Kim
  - Notre Dame, Stanford Promo, 10/07/2000; 00-1007-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    A promo for a football game between Stanford and Notre Dame.
  - The Inauguration of John Hennessy as the Tenth President of Stanford University, 10/20/2000; 00-1020-2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP L) (Box 7)
    Length: 01:26:48
    Presented by the Stanford Channel, Building 590, Room 103, has a Post-it note with "Hubbard" on it. President John Hennessy invited the community to engage in a dialogue on Stanford's future, saying in his inaugural address Friday that the university is well positioned to maintain and prosper as, in Leland and Jane Stanford's words, "a University of high degree.
  - William Hewlett Memorial, News Segments, 01/19/2001 - 01/20/2001; 01-0119-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Length: 01:09:20
    Services for William (Bill) Hewlett at Stanford Memorial Church. The co-founder and former president of Hewlett-Packard Co. was remembered for his philanthropy, curiosity, love of nature and music, good humor and stubborn streak--characteristics that stood out as much as his role in launching two multibillion-dollar, multinational high-tech corporations. Clips from KRON, Bay TV, KNTV, KNTV, KGO: 1/19/01 5:15 PM KRON; 1/19/01 6:18 PM KRON; 1/19/01 9:32 PM BAYTV; 1/20/01 5:05 PM KRON; 1/20/01 10:17 PM KTVU; 1/20/01 9:12 PM BAYTV; 1/20/01 11:11 PM KNTV; 1/20/01 11:13 PM KRON; 1/20/01 11:15 PM KGO
  - Anthrax Scare, 10/30/2001; 01-1030-4; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
    Anthrax scare that caused the Risk Management Office to be evacuated at 651 Serra St.
  - Stanford Promo, 08/08/1995; 95-0808-5; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
  - Karen Nierenberg Standups, Graduate School of Business, 08/14/1995; 95-0814-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Karen Nierenberg, Director of Development, Standups 3:55 or 5:58 Opening; 8:54 (sun on nose?) or 9:47 Entrepreneurship; 10:47 (eye blinks) or 11:07 Executive Education; 11:40 Alumni; 17:04 or 19:14 Close
  - David Kreps interview, 08/18/1995; 95-0818-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    David Kreps interview 1995 Professor of economics at Stanford Graduate School of Business
  - "A Letter from Stanford" GSB, Master, 08/30/1995; 95-0830-2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Length: 00:11:16
    Admission Video Video letter to new students Micheal Spence Garth Saloner Chuck Holloway William P Madar
  - "A Letter from Stanford" GSB, Master, Dub, 08/30/1995; 95-0830-3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Admission Video Video letter to new students; Micheal Spence; Garth Saloner; Chuck Holloway; William P Madar; Tape contains a note: Return to Hubbard
  - Stanford "Counter" spot, 09/13/1995; 95-0913-2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
  - Stanford "Counter" spot, 09/13/1995; 95-0913-3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    [No further information is available. ] Counter Spot
  - Martin Perl, Nobel Prize, Press Conference, Original, 10/11/1995; 95-1011-3a; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 8)
    Martin Lewis Perl is a Stanford physicist, who won the Nobel Prize in Physics in 1995 for his discovery of the tau lepton. Tape contains arrival and applause of Nobel winner Perl and former Nobel winners Richard Taylor and Burton Richter.
  - Martin Perl, Nobel Prize, Press Conference, Lab, Original, 10/11/1995; 95-1011-3b; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 8)
    Martin Lewis Perl is a Stanford physicist, who won the Nobel Prize in Physics in 1995 for his discovery of the tau lepton. Tape contains end of press conference and Martin Perl in his lab.
  - Martin Perl, Nobel Prize, Press Conference, Original, 10/11/1995; 95-1011-3c; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 8)
    Martin Lewis Perl is a Stanford physicist, who won the Nobel Prize in Physics in 1995 for his discovery of the tau lepton. Tape contains poetry from Gerhard Casper, Condoleezza Rice, and Burton Richter. Then speeches by Burton Richter, Gerhard Casper, Burton Richter and Martin Pearl
  - Reflections on the O.J. Simpson trial - Tape #1, 10/13/1995; 95-1013-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Kim Taylor-Thompson, Stanford law professor O.J. Simpson Tape contains a Broadcast Release form from Kim Taylor-Thompson.
  - Reflections on the O.J. Simpson trial - Tape #2, 10/13/1995; 95-1013-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Kim Taylor-Thompson, Stanford law professor O.J. Simpson
  - Stanford Museum, (Cantor Art Museum), 10/20/1995; 95-1020-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Stanford Museum 1995 San Francisco; Polshek and Partners; Museum of Art meeting with Thomas Seligman; [Stanford University used Polshek and Partners of New York and San Francisco as architects for the project to renovate and expand the Stanford University Museum of A t. The project will result in the establishment of the Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Center for the Visual Arts at Stanford.]
  - Graduate School of Business - Alumni Association Reunion - Tape #1, 10/21/1995; 95-1021-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Tape contains a Drop Frame.
  - Graduate School of Business - Alumni Association Reunion - Tape #2, 10/21/1995; 95-1021-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Tape contains Drop Frame.
  - Stanford Museum Groundbreaking- Tape 1, 10/26/1995; 95-1026-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Stanford Museum 1995 Art museum groundbreaking Interview with Director Thomas Seligman, Architect James Polshek, and Architect Richard Olcott Schmoozing - Ruth Halperin, donor A complete renovation of the earthquake- damaged Stanford University Museum of Art and the construction of a new 40,000-square-foot wing are scheduled to begin in October. The new complex, including the museum and the Rodin Sculpture Garden, will be known as the Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Center for the Visual Arts, in recognition of a $10 million gift the Cantors made in 1994.
  - Stanford Museum Groundbreaking - Tape 2, 10/26/1995; 95-1026-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Stanford Museum 1995 Art museum groundbreaking ceremonies A complete renovation of the earthquake- damaged Stanford University Museum of Art and the construction of a new 40,000-square-foot wing are scheduled to begin in October. The new complex, including the museum and the Rodin Sculpture Garden, will be known as the Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Center for the Visual Arts, in recognition of a $10 million gift the Cantors made in 1994.
  - Stanford Museum Groundbreaking - Tape 3, 10/26/1995; 95-1026-1c; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Stanford Art museum groundbreaking Stairway, Iris Cantor A complete renovation of the earthquake- damaged Stanford University Museum of Art and the construction of a new 40,000-square-foot wing are scheduled to begin in October. The new complex, including the museum and the Rodin Sculpture Garden, will be known as the Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Center for the Visual Arts, in recognition of a $10 million gift the Cantors made in 1994.
  - Douglas Osheroff (14), 11/15/1995; 95-1115-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Length: 14:05:46
    Douglas Osheroff, Physics Professor (awarded Nobel Prize for physics in 1996) Stanford #14
  - Stanford #13, Douglas Osheroff, 11/15/1995; 95-1115-2; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Douglas Osheroff, Physics Professor (awarded Nobel Prize for physics in 1996), from 13:17:46 to end of tape Stanford #13
  - Monterey Bay Aquarium near Shore Habitats - B-roll, 02/00/1996 - 03/00/1996; 96-0200-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Monterey Bay Aquarium near Shore Habitats - B-roll Bars/black; Monterey Bay Aquarium logo; Monterey Bay - establishing shoreline shots; Aerial of aquarium; Main entrance exterior (wide and medium shots); Interior near main entrance with hanging orca models; Great Tidepool deck area; Kelp Forest exhibit; Anchovy school in Kelp Forest; Kelp Forest sunny detail; Kelp Forest feeding show with diver; Diver underwater in Kelp Forest; Visitor reactions to exhibits; Monterey Bay Habitats exhibit; Fish closeups in Monterey Bay Habitats; Food preparation for sea otter exhibit; Feeding sharks in Monterey Bay Habitats exhibit; Shark eating from visitor viewing area; Animal closeups: Pacific giant octopus, chambered nautilus, cuttlefish, sand dabs, hermit crabs, wolf eel and ling cod, sea pen, skate egg case, borrowing anemone; Wharf piling exhibit; Wharf community exhibit (medium and closeup shots of fish); Rocky Shores gallery (anemone, sea hare, hermit crab); Abalone in Kelp Gallery; Ghost shrimp in Slough Gallery; Pipe fish in Slough Gallery; Sandy Shore Aviary including bird closeups; Bat Ray touch pool; Touch Pool; Coastal Stream exhibit; Wave crash exhibit; Great Tidepool with surrogate mother and sea otter pup; Kelp Forest exhibit - various angles; Visitor reaction shots; Anchovy exhibit (closeups and medium shots); Sheep crab with visitors; Kelp Lab - various angles; Sea Otters Along the Rocky Coast (from above exhibit and from visitor area, various angles); The Outer Bay at the Monterey Bay Aquarium Bars/tone Sunset over Monterey Bay; Dolphins in Monterey Bay; Aerial of Monterey Bay Aquarium; Exterior of Monterey Bay Aquarium with bay in background; Exterior of The Outer Bay wing from bay side of building; Outer Bay intro area; 360º anchovy exhibit with visitors; Anchovies; Swimmer/Drifters intro area with visitors; Pacific Mackerel exhibit with visitors; Pacific Mackerel closeup; Drifters Gallery with visitors; Sea nettle exhibit with visitors; Sea nettles (medium and closeup shots); Purple striped jelly closeup; Drifters Gallery reverse angle with visitors; Comb jelly closeup; Egg yolk jelly closeup; Jelly interactive with visitors; Tiny Drifters Gallery with visitors; pan to The Outer Bay with Outer Bay exhibit in background; Outer Bay exhibit with visitors from mezzanine; Outer Bay exhibit from various angles (wide, medium and closeups) with visitors; Sardine exhibit with visitors; Closeup of sardines; Exploring the Outer Bay Gallery including "Under a Lens" and "Out to Sea"; Ocean Travelers Gallery with visitors; Flippers, Flukes and Fun area with visitors; Underwater in Outer Bay exhibit; Mola feeding; Mola collecting; Assembled February/March 1996
  - Deborah Gordon ants - Tape 1, 04/11/1996; 96-0411-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Deborah Gordon, Biology Professor Teaching class; Ant experiments; Interview
  - Deborah Gordon, Ants - Tape 2, 04/11/1996; 96-0411-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Deborah Gordon, Biology Professor Ants labs; Close-ups; Pointing
  - Stanford Museum, 04/29/1996; 96-0429-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Stanford Museum 1996 Home wreckers; Construction; Demolition; Structures; Bulldozers
  - Stanford's Center for the Study of Language and Information (CSLI), Archimedes, 05/09/1996; 96-0509-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    CSLI - Archimedes Voice-speech input; Robert Edings; Neil Scott; Learning the Computer; Scott briefs; Short interview; the Archimedes Project was founded at Stanford University in 1990 as an independent research organization, It studies barriers to accessing and using information, computers, and information appliances and identifies and designs innovative solutions, including accessors, that advance universal access to and use of information and control of one's environment.
  - Stanford's Center for the Study of Language and Information (CSLI), Archimedes, 05/09/1996; 96-0509-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    CSLI 1996 Robert Edings; J.B. Golan; Neil Scott; Yoshi and Neil do a computer loading drill; the Archimedes Project was founded at Stanford University in 1990 as an independent research organization, It studies barriers to accessing and using information, computers, and information appliances and identifies and designs innovative solutions, including accessors, that advance universal access to and use of information and control of one's environment.
  - Stanford's Center for the Study of Language and Information (CSLI), Archimedes, 05/09/1996; 96-0509-1c; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    CSLI - Archimedes 1996 Disabled people using computers; the Archimedes Project was founded at Stanford University in 1990 as an independent research organization, It studies barriers to accessing and using information, computers, and information appliances and identifies and designs innovative solutions, including accessors, that advance universal access to and use of information and control of one's environment.
  - Stanford's Center for the Study of Language and Information (CSLI), Archimedes, 05/09/1996; 96-0509-1d; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    CSLI - Archimedes 1996 the Archimedes Project was founded at Stanford University in 1990 as an independent research organization, It studies barriers to accessing and using information, computers, and information appliances and identifies and designs innovative solutions, including accessors, that advance universal access to and use of information and control of one's environment.
  - Charles Kruger and Ramon Saldivar Education Initiatives, 05/09/1996; 96-0509-2a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
    Vice-Provost for Undergraduate Education Ramon Saldivar, and vice-provost, Charles Kruger initiatives Briefing Two initiatives to strengthen both undergraduate and graduate education at Stanford were announced by President Gerhard Casper. The first of these concerns new programs for first- and second-year undergraduates. They expanded the faculty to provide greater teaching capacity, while simultaneously strengthening the research capabilities. Plans will be reviewed by a new advisory board, to be chaired by Vice-Provost for Undergraduate Education Ramon Saldivar. The second initiative is intended to provide new support for graduate students ­ primarily, but not exclusively, in the sciences and engineering. It will enables them to compete effectively for the best graduate students and to maintain the strength of graduate programs even as they cope with the stresses caused by decreased research support from the federal government. Dean Kruger has organized a steering committee of senior faculty to finalize the details of this program and advise the provost on the distribution of awards.
  - Charles Kruger and Ramon Saldivar Education Initiatives, 05/09/1996; 96-0509-2b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 8)
  - Japan's Royal Couple Visit Stanford, 06/23/1994 - 06/24/1994; 94-0623-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 9)
    VMS (Video Monitor Services of America) tape contains stories about the Japanese Royalty visit to Stanford. News at Ten, KTLA-TV (IND) Los Angeles, 10:00 - 11:00pm, Morning News, KTLA-TV (IND) Los Angeles, 6:00 - 7:00am
  - Visit of Emperor and Empress of Japan to SLAC, June 23, 1994; 94-0623-2; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 9)
    The Emperor and Empress of japan visited the Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, where Japanese physicists are part of an international collaboration. The visit began at the Stanford Linear Accelerator Center's visitors' center around 11:45 a.m. Members of the American media, consular officials, Secret Service agents and SLAC staffers wearing badges that said "Japan-USA Cooperation at SLAC" assembled early to await the arrival of the imperial couple's entourage, which included members of the Japanese press corps. A staff member from the Japanese consulate in San Francisco explained that the SLAC visit was scheduled to highlight that Japan is part of a 40-country consortium working on high- energy physics at SLAC.
  - Stephen Breyer Confirmation Hearings C-Span, Tape 1, 07/14/1994; 94-0714-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 9)
    Confirmation hearings for the Supreme court of Stephen Breyer in front of the Senate. There was a panel with President Gerhard Casper and Law Professor Kathleen Sullivan.
  - Stephen Breyer Confirmation Hearings C-Span, Tape B, 07/14/1994; 94-0714-2a; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 9)
    Confirmation hearings for the Supreme court of Stanford Alum Stephen Breyer in front of the Senate.
  - Stephen Breyer Confirmation Hearings C-Span, Tape C, 07/14/1994; 94-0714-2b; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 9)
  - Stanford University Researchers study earthquake damage, 08/16/1994; 94-0816-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 9)
    1.) The Money Wheel, CNBC-TV Cable 12:30 PM :026 2.) Channel 7 News at Six, KGO-TV (ABC) San Francisco, 6:00 PM 2:01 3.) Eyewitness News Nightcast, KPIX-TV (CBS) San Francisco, 10:00, 2:31 4. Ten O'Clock News, KTVU-TV (IND) San Francisco, 10:00 PM, 3:03
  - Linus Pauling Funeral / Mountain Lion Near Stanford, 08/29/1994 - 09/10/1994; 94-0829-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 9)
    Linus Pauling Funeral Ten O'Clock News, 8/29/94, KTVU-TV (IND) Oakland 10:00 PM 3:14 two-time Nobel Prize winner, Linus C. Pauling, served on the Stanford faculty from 1969 to 1973. Mountain Lion Near Stanford; Live at Five, 9/10/94, KRON-TV (NBC) San Francisco 5:00 PM, 2:21
  - World Economic Forum, 09/19/1994; 94-0919-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 9)
    Length: 00:03:07
    Eyewitness News, KPIX-TV (CBS), San Francisco, 10:00 PM, 3:07, Master Copy